https://baumancollege.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Bauman College uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.
Bauman College is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.
Bauman College may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Therefore, we suggest that you check back periodically to ensure that you are comfortable with any changes.
What We Collect
We may collect the following information in order to provide information and/or services to you when you use our website information request forms, subscribe to newsletters, or contact our customer service representatives by phone. We only collect personally identifiable information that you submit voluntarily, including:
Name and job title
Contact information including email address and phone number
Demographic information such as zip code, mailing address, preferences, and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What We Do With the Information We Gather
Bauman College collects personal information only with the express consent of the user when they request information from our organization. This information is only used when communicating with users per their indicated preferences and as needed for service-related communications. We may use the information you provide to:
Keep internal records
Improve our products and services
Send promotional communications about special offers or other information via email which we think you may find interesting
Contact you for market research purposes, from time to time. We may contact you by email, phone, fax, or mail.
Customize the website according to your interests
Opting Out
Bauman College provides users with the ability to opt out of communications from any of our newsletters. An opt-out option will either appear at the bottom of a newsletter received by email, or users can reply directly to the emailed newsletter and request removal from that correspondence.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How We Use Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or tracks when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
I Want Answers
Can I get financial aid?
My career prospects?
How much is tuition?
When does it start?
Program*Choose a ProgramNutrition Consultant – OnlineHolistic Chef – OnlineCampus*BerkeleyName*
First
Last
Email*
Where do you live?*United StatesOutside the United StatesState*Select your state…AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingPhone*How Did You Hear about Bauman?Web SearchFacebook/InstagramReferred by someoneEvent PostcardPrint AdOtherBy completing and submitting this form, you are providing consent without obligation, for Bauman College to contact you by phone, text, email or automated means about your education at the number and/or email address provided.EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Privacy Policy
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
What our graduates say
I’m thrilled to be a graduate of Bauman College! I feel equipped to educate and empower others on their journey toward better health!
more
Partners + Affiliates
Get Info!
×
X
